Last update: 4/27/2022



Kourosh Ahmadzadeh Ataei

Gmail | in Github | in Linkedin

Personal Data

Address: No.226, Dehkhoda 7 St., Piruzi Blvd., Mashhad, IRAN.

Mobile: +989036928421

Date of birth: December 19, 1996. (25 years)

Place of birth: Ferdows, IRAN

Education

Ferdowsi University of Mashhad (FUM)

Bachelor of Computer Engineering GPA 15.56/20 (3.31 GPA)

• Last 2 years GPA is 16.59 (3.52 GPA)

 Relevant Coursework: Data Mining – Algorithm Design - Database - Information Retrieval -Artificial Intelligence – Web Development - Data communication – Multimedia systems - Data Structures

Areas of Interests

Web development – Rest API - Blockchain - Software engineering - Information Retrieval – Data Mining - Computer Vision - Deep learning, Machine learning

Experience

Junior Software Engineer, Co-Founder Al Trader startup (Aran Accelerator)

I am responsible for:

- Develop platform base on python
- Develop telegram bot for front
- Work with MySQL

Main achievement:

- Acquire team management Teamwork
- Learn and Implement Pattern Designs

Sysadmin for server side

Product manager

pattern designs

Mashhad, IRAN

Sep. 2016 - Sep. 2021

Jun. 2022 – Feb. 2022

Last update: 4/27/2022

R&D Developer Jun. 2022 – Feb. 2022

Green Render Startup (Aran Accelerator)

I am responsible for:

- Sysadmin Linux(ubuntu-centos)
- Work with PostgreSQL

Main achievement:

- learn server-side commands and bash script
- Configure render farm multi-GPUs
- learn research and development

Swift Developer Intern

Jul. 2020 - Sep. 2020

Part software

I am responsible for:

 Develop IOS applications based on swift and objective-c

Main achievement:

- Learn advance GIT
- Learn swift and IOS development

- Learn swift and XCode
- Do tasks and small project

Selected Projects

Work

• Teamus website Feb. 2022 – Present

Developed a web application for team and persons CVs & Resumes

- Based on Django python
- App provides team creation and write their CVs for customers
- Cryptocurrency bot API

Apr. 2022 – Present

Develop an API for cryptocurrency bots

- Based on Django rest framework
 - o App provides strategies and auto trading for customers with purchase plans

Academic

Charity website (Thesis project)

Winter 2020

Developed a web application for charities and restaurant

- Based on PHP and MySQL
- The project involves a free food distribution system in which restaurants serve some extra food at the end of each day.

Mstpd UI
 Winter 2020

Data communication, Prof.A. Hosseini, FUM

 Multiple Spanning Tree Protocol Daemon python CLI project with configure and installation on Ubuntu

Last update: 4/27/2022

 Optimization on TF-IDF recommender system Fall 2020

Basics of information retrieval and web search, Prof.F.Ensan, FUM.

- Implemented an optimization on classical TF-IDF algorithm and proposed adaptive weight of position of word algorithm based on TF-IDF
- Network security API

Winter 2019

Fundamentals of Secure Computing, Prof.H.Amintoosi, FUM

- Django Rest API [POST, GET, PUT] for check ports, show user logs, Token Authentication
 System, check available website user requests, DDos prevention
- <u>Air Hockey</u> Winter 2016

Advanced Programming, Prof.A.Nouri Baygi, FUM

JavaFx game application with AI agent

Skills

Languages: Python, familiar with SQL, Solidity, Html, CSS, Java, PHP, Swift, bash script, Redis

Libraries: NumPy, Pandas, Web3, Socket, Lucene, JavaFx, Multithreading

Technologies: Django, Django REST framework, MySQL, WordPress, Git, PyCharm, Google Colab, XCode,

CEH, MVC, Design Patterns, Scrum, fast API, Telegram bot, photoshop

Languages: English: Upper Intermediate, Persian: Native

About Me

I learned all of my big major of these skills independently although I am willing to teamwork. Learning new languages and frameworks enable me to research and develop more and more. I am flexible and responsible in work and learn quickly. Nowadays, I am working with python and solidity.